Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم الإدارة، شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
[The Glory of Queen]
[مجد الملكة]
[Episode 6]
[الحلقة 6]
Miss, this is freshly made puffed rice.
يا آنسة، هذا أرز منتفخ طازج.
It's sweet and crispy.
إنه حلو ومقرمش.
Shall I get a portion for you and your husband?
هل أحضر حصة لكِ ولزوجكِ؟
No.
لا.
He's not my husband.
هو ليس زوجي.
We don't need it. Thank you.
لسنا بحاجة إليه. شكراً لك.
All right.
حسنًا.
Eldest Young Master,
السيد الشاب الأكبر،
we should keep some distance as we walk,
ينبغي أن نحافظ على مسافة معينة أثناء سيرنا.
so no one gets the wrong idea.
حتى لا يفهم أحد الأمر بشكل خاطئ.
I'm just a maid,
أنا مجرد خادمة،
I wouldn't want to embarrass you.
لا أريد أن أحرجك.
Do not think so little of yourself.
لا تقلل من شأن نفسك.
Being able to learn fragrance-making from Jingheng
القدرة على تعلم صناعة العطور من جينغهينغ
proves your extraordinary talent.
يثبت ذلك موهبتك الاستثنائية.
With such ability,
بهذه القدرة،
you will never be confined to the role of a mere maid in the Pei Manor.
لن تقتصر مهمتك أبدًا على دور مجرد خادمة في قصر باي.
This is for you.
هذا لك.
What is this?
ما هذا؟
Noticing your love for sweets,
لاحظت حبك للحلويات،
I thought I'd bribe you a little
فكرت أن أرشوك قليلاً
before you become successful.
قبل أن تحقق النجاح.
Sure. When I've made it,
بالتأكيد. عندما أنجز ذلك،
I won't say no to anything
لن أرفض أي شيء
you need help with.
أنت بحاجة إلى مساعدة في.
All right.
حسنًا.
Don't say I didn't give you a good deal.
لا تقل إني لم أقدم لك عرضاً جيداً.
You won't find these goods
لن تجد هذه البضائع
cheaper anywhere else in Wu County.
أرخص في أي مكان آخر في مقاطعة وو.
Isn't that your elder brother?
أليس هذا أخاك الأكبر؟
Who's the woman beside him?
من هي المرأة التي بجانبه؟
She's gorgeous.
إنها رائعة الجمال.
They're a perfect match.
إنهما متوافقان تماماً.
The Meng family is big and rich,
عائلة مينغ كبيرة وغنية،
and the Pei family buys far more than others.
وتشتري عائلة باي أكثر بكثير من غيرها.
So the cost price
لذا سعر التكلفة
should be lower.
ينبغي أن يكون أقل.
Let's lower it by another twenty percent.
لنخفضها بنسبة عشرين بالمائة أخرى.
Pei Jingheng,
باي جينغ هينج
you might as well take them for free!
يمكنك أخذها مجاناً!
Dusters.
منفضة الغبار.
Take a look.
ألقِ نظرة.
They are very durable.
إنها متينة للغاية.
What's that?
ما هذا؟
Come and take a look.
تعال وألق نظرة.
Come with me. Let's go take a look.
تعال معي. لنذهب ونلقي نظرة.
They are all on sale today.
جميعها معروضة للبيع اليوم.
On the last day of the Fragrance Festival,
في اليوم الأخير من مهرجان العطور،
there'll be a Fragrance Competition.
ستُقام مسابقة للعطور.
Today's the last day to sign up.
اليوم هو آخر يوم للتسجيل.
What do they actually compete in
في أي مجال يتنافسون فعلياً؟
at the Fragrance Competition?
في مسابقة العطور؟
It's the same stuff you've been learning.
إنها نفس الأشياء التي كنت تتعلمها.
Back then, this part
في ذلك الوقت، هذا الجزء
was meant to select people in the county
كان الهدف هو اختيار أشخاص من المقاطعة
with a talent for fragrance-making.
يتمتع بموهبة في صناعة العطور.
Nowadays, it has been carried on
في الوقت الحاضر، استمر الأمر
as the Pei family's way
على طريقة عائلة باي
of selecting talents for themselves.
اختيار المواهب لأنفسهم.
Nowadays, in Wu County,
في الوقت الحاضر، في مقاطعة وو،
the Pei family dominates the fragrance-making industry.
تسيطر عائلة باي على صناعة العطور.
Even if the winner of the Fragrance Competition
حتى لو كان الفائز في مسابقة العطور
isn't from the Pei family,
ليس من عائلة باي،
they will ultimately be recruited by them.
سيتم تجنيدهم في نهاية المطاف من قبلهم.
You're very smart.
أنت ذكي جداً.
By the way, Eldest Young Master,
بالمناسبة، يا سيدنا الشاب الأكبر،
since Wu County is so big,
نظراً لكبر مساحة مقاطعة وو،
are there no other fragrance shops around?
ألا توجد متاجر عطور أخرى في الجوار؟
There used to be other shops,
كانت هناك متاجر أخرى في السابق،
but they all closed
لكنهم جميعًا أغلقوا
because they couldn't compete with the Pei family.
لأنهم لم يتمكنوا من منافسة عائلة باي.
By now, who would dare to challenge the Pei family
من يجرؤ الآن على تحدي عائلة باي؟
in this business?
في هذا المجال؟
Aunt Ping's fragrance shop did very well back then.
حقق متجر العطور الخاص بالعمة بينغ نجاحًا كبيرًا في ذلك الوقت.
There's no way it couldn't compete with the Pei family.
لا يمكن بأي حال من الأحوال ألا تتمكن من منافسة عائلة باي.
The Pei family rules the industry.
تسيطر عائلة باي على هذه الصناعة.
On the surface, it's their skill;
ظاهرياً، الأمر يتعلق بمهارتهم؛
but looking closer,
لكن بالتدقيق أكثر،
the Pei family may have deliberately monopolized the trade.
ربما تكون عائلة باي قد احتكرت التجارة عمداً.
Aunt Ping's disappearance back then
اختفاء العمة بينغ في ذلك الوقت
was probably connected to this.
ربما كان ذلك مرتبطًا بهذا.
I need to hurry and find Ergou and the others.
عليّ الإسراع والعثور على إرغو والآخرين.
What's on your mind?
ما الذي يدور في ذهنك؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
Oh, Eldest Young Master,
يا سيدي الشاب الأكبر،
I just remembered
تذكرت للتو
that Second Young Master had some tasks for me,
كان لدى السيد الشاب الثاني بعض المهام لي،
and I completely forgot.
ونسيت الأمر تماماً.
Let's come out another time.
لنخرج في وقت آخر.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
You won't sign up for the competition?
ألن تسجل في المسابقة؟
I won't.
أنا لن.
Why are you still awake at this hour?
لماذا ما زلت مستيقظاً في هذه الساعة؟
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
You scared me.
لقد أرعبتني.
So you remembered to come back.
إذن تذكرت أن تعود.
I admit I came back a bit late today.
أعترف أنني عدت متأخراً بعض الشيء اليوم.
A bit late?
متأخر قليلاً؟
Looks like you've been out fooling around
يبدو أنك كنت تلهو وتعبث.
with someone until now.
مع شخص ما حتى الآن.
I just got carried away and lost track of time.
لقد انجرفت في اللحظة وفقدتُ الإحساس بالوقت.
I wasn't fooling around.
لم أكن أمزح.
Besides,
بجانب،
I've been thinking about you,
كنت أفكر فيك،
and I even brought you something nice.
بل وأحضرت لك شيئاً جميلاً.
Your leftovers.
بقايا طعامك.
Is this how you've been thinking of me?
هل هذه هي الطريقة التي كنت تفكر بها بي؟
No.
لا.
This is really good.
هذا جيد حقاً.
You definitely haven't tried it before.
من المؤكد أنك لم تجرب ذلك من قبل.
Give it a taste.
جربها.
Here.
هنا.
You...
أنت...
Why are you being so stubborn and unreasonable?
لماذا أنت عنيد وغير منطقي إلى هذا الحد؟
You're unbelievable!
أنت لا تُصدق!
I brought this back for you,
أحضرت هذا من أجلك،
even though I wanted it myself.
على الرغم من أنني كنت أريده بنفسي.
Why are you yelling at me?
لماذا تصرخ في وجهي؟
The Fragrance Festival is only a couple of days away.
لم يتبق سوى يومين على مهرجان العطور .
After giving it some thought,
بعد التفكير في الأمر قليلاً،
I've decided that Jingheng will host it this year.
لقد قررت أن يستضيف جينغهينغ الحدث هذا العام.
No!
لا!
I've been the one hosting
لقد كنتُ أنا من يستضيف الفعالية
the Fragrance Festival every year.
مهرجان العطور كل عام.
You should just focus on finding the fragrance manual.
يجب عليك التركيز فقط على إيجاد دليل العطور.
You did say
لقد قلت ذلك
that if you couldn't recover it…
أنه إذا لم تتمكن من استعادته...
Fragrance manual… Day after day, it's all you can talk about.
دليل العطور... يوماً بعد يوم، لا يمكنك التحدث إلا عنه.
If I don't get it back,
إذا لم أستردها،
will I no longer be the Pei family's eldest legitimate daughter?
هل سأفقد بعد الآن كوني الابنة الشرعية الكبرى لعائلة باي ؟
Xiuning, Mother is just...
شيونينغ، أمي هي فقط...
Shut it!
أغلقه!
Stop pretending.
توقف عن التظاهر.
You just want to see me fail, don't you?
أنت تريد فقط أن تراني أفشل، أليس كذلك؟
Not a chance.
مستحيل.
He was too young before,
كان صغيراً جداً في السابق،
but now
لكن الآن
that he can handle things on his own,
أنه يستطيع التعامل مع الأمور بمفرده،
Mother has him host the Fragrance Competition.
تطلب منه والدته استضافة مسابقة العطور.
Isn't it obvious
أليس هذا واضحاً؟
she favors Pei Jingheng as her heir?
هل تفضل باي جينغهنغ كوريث لها؟
Then what about me?
وماذا عني أنا؟
My Lady.
سيدتي.
My Lady, please calm down.
سيدتي، أرجو أن تهدئي.
Shut up!
اسكت!
You're no good either.
أنت لست جيدًا أيضًا.
Since you started taking the medicine at the beginning of the year,
بما أنك بدأت بتناول الدواء في بداية العام،
that thing of yours still isn't working.
لا يزال ذلك الشيء الذي لديك لا يعمل.
If you can't do anything right,
إذا لم تستطع فعل أي شيء بشكل صحيح،
then get out of the Pei Manor!
ثم اخرج من قصر باي!
My Lady,
سيدتي،
it's all my fault.
كل هذا خطأي.
After all these years,
بعد كل هذه السنوات،
I still haven't given you a single child.
لم أرزقك بطفل واحد حتى الآن.
(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
(شاهد على www.dramacool.club دعم الإدارة)
But… But I've found
لكن... لكنني وجدت
two more obedient and sensible men.
رجلان آخران مطيعان وعاقلان.
The physician has already checked.
لقد قام الطبيب بالفحص بالفعل.
They are both fit to have children.
كلاهما مؤهلان لإنجاب الأطفال.
Once they enter the manor,
بمجرد دخولهم القصر،
I'll have them serve you.
سأطلب منهم أن يخدموك.
We'll do our best
سنبذل قصارى جهدنا
to help you become pregnant as soon as possible.
لمساعدتك على الحمل في أسرع وقت ممكن.
Look at you, all timid and submissive.
انظر إليك، خجول وخاضع.
You're truly spineless.
أنت حقاً عديم الشخصية.
Can't you do something useful for me?
ألا يمكنك أن تفعل شيئاً مفيداً لي؟
Really?
حقًا؟
Yes.
نعم.
So you'll do anything for me?
إذن ستفعل أي شيء من أجلي؟
Does it hurt?
هل يؤلمك؟
If it does,
إذا حدث ذلك،
make sure you remember
تأكد من أنك تتذكر
the promise you just made to me.
الوعد الذي قطعته لي للتو.
I have an idea,
لدي فكرة،
one that would totally prevent
واحد من شأنه أن يمنع تمامًا
Second Young Master from competing with you.
ثاني شاب محترف يتفوق عليك في المنافسة.
Eldest Young Master, that's truly impressive.
يا سيدنا الشاب الأكبر، هذا أمر مثير للإعجاب حقاً.
You can even do this?
هل يمكنك فعل هذا؟
A man's duty
واجب الرجل
is to marry and raise children.
هو الزواج وإنجاب الأطفال.
Knowing more about household affairs can come in handy.
معرفة المزيد عن شؤون المنزل قد تكون مفيدة.
With your skill and dexterity,
بفضل مهارتك وبراعتك،
it's not only household affairs you can manage,
لا تقتصر قدرتك على إدارة شؤون المنزل فقط،
but you can also accomplish anything
لكن يمكنك أيضاً تحقيق أي شيء
you set your mind to.
أنت الذي عزمت عليه.
Here, try it yourself.
جرب بنفسك.
I don't know how.
لا أعرف كيف.
I'll teach you. Come.
سأعلمك. تعال.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Here, pinch it slightly.
هنا، اضغط عليه قليلاً.
What are you two doing?
ماذا تفعلان؟
Why are you sneaking around
لماذا تتسلل هنا وهناك؟
like a ghost?
مثل الشبح؟
In broad daylight,
في وضح النهار،
the Pei family's Eldest Young Master
السيد الشاب الأكبر لعائلة باي
and a maid,
وخادمة،
so flirty and intimate.
مرحة وحميمية للغاية.
How improper.
يا له من أمر غير لائق.
How is that flirty and intimate?
كيف يكون ذلك مغازلة وحميمية؟
It's your filthy mind
إنه عقلك القذر
that sees it that way.
من يرى الأمر بهذه الطريقة.
I invited Zhiyao to try the pastries I made.
دعوتُ تشياو لتجربة المعجنات التي صنعتها.
If you don't like it,
إذا لم يعجبك ذلك،
I'll keep my distance in the future.
سأحافظ على مسافة بيننا في المستقبل.
"Zhiyao"?
"زيياو"؟
Sounds like you two are quite close.
يبدو أنكما مقربان جداً.
Eldest Young Master, here's the thing:
يا سيدي الشاب الأكبر، إليك الأمر:
Second Young Master
السيد الشاب الثاني
simply doesn't like me.
ببساطة، لا يحبني.
I'll let you get on with your business.
سأتركك تتابع أعمالك.
We'll leave now.
سنغادر الآن.
Eldest Young Master, didn't you say
أيها السيد الشاب الأكبر، ألم تقل
you'd take me somewhere fun?
هل ستأخذني إلى مكان ممتع؟
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
So this is the Pei family’s Treasure Pavilion.
إذن هذا هو جناح الكنوز الخاص بعائلة باي.
Zhiyao,
زياو،
besides making fragrances,
إلى جانب صناعة العطور،
there are many interesting things
هناك العديد من الأشياء المثيرة للاهتمام
and fascinating people in this world.
وأشخاص رائعون في هذا العالم.
Is there anything you like?
هل هناك شيء يعجبك؟
I'll give it to you.
سأعطيك إياه.
That won't be necessary.
لن يكون ذلك ضرورياً.
These are far too valuable.
هذه الأشياء ثمينة للغاية.
Eldest Young Master.
السيد الشاب الأكبر.
What's the matter?
ماذا جرى؟
Have you noticed any strange smells?
هل لاحظت أي روائح غريبة؟
No.
لا.
What's wrong? Are you all right?
ما الخطب؟ هل أنت بخير؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Watch out!
انتبه!
♪The secret about you is buried deep in my heart♪
♪سرّك مدفونٌ في أعماق قلبي♪
♪I draw near, then pull away, fearing I might yield to this attraction♪
♪أقترب، ثم أبتعد، خوفاً من أن أستسلم لهذا الانجذاب♪
♪I like to think I'm keeping my cool♪
أحب أن أعتقد أنني أحافظ على هدوئي.
♪But my instincts keep pulling me closer♪
لكن غرائزي تستمر في جذبي إلى أقرب نقطة
♪Unwittingly, I've fallen completely for you♪
♪دون أن أدري، وقعت في حبك تماماً♪
♪Can the sacrifices of this life measure the depth of love?♪
هل يمكن لتضحيات هذه الحياة أن تقيس عمق الحب؟
♪It's too late to summon the courage to hold you once more♪
♪لقد فات الأوان لاستجماع الشجاعة لاحتضانك مرة أخرى♪
♪Having witnessed all the world's splendor♪
♪بعد أن شهدنا كل روعة العالم♪
♪I've felt joy and sorrow for one soul alone♪
♪شعرت بالفرح والحزن من أجل روح واحدة فقط♪
♪For our kindred souls, all I can give is this humble heart♪
♪لأرواحنا المتآلفة، كل ما أستطيع تقديمه هو هذا القلب المتواضع♪
♪If I encounter you in this life♪
♪إذا صادفتك في هذه الحياة♪
♪Fate is already fulfilled♪
♪لقد تحقق القدر بالفعل♪
♪Let this chapter become a memory, breaking free from destiny♪
♪دع هذا الفصل يصبح ذكرى، متحرراً من قيود القدر♪
♪In the next life, may the course of time lead me to you♪
♪في الحياة الأخرى، أتمنى أن يقودني الزمن إليك♪
♪With a sincere heart, I shall carry our love forward♪
♪بقلبٍ صادق، سأحمل حبنا إلى الأمام♪